<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Pokemon Tricks</string>


    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="action_add_favourite">Add to Favourites</string>
    <string name="action_play_next">Play Next</string>
    <string name="backdrop_title">Love PokemonGo</string>
    <string name="backdrop_subtitle">This season top 20 Tricks</string>

    <string name="desc_1">You want to hear how your Pokémon sounds, right? Who doesn\'t? Tap the Pokéball at the bottom of the screen, select the Pokémon submenu, and select which Pokémon you want to hear. When their character screen comes up, tap on the Pokémon itself. If your volume isn\'t up, turn it up. Now you can hear \'em!</string>
    <string name="desc_2">While capturing Pokémon, you may have seen an XP bonus on your capture that says "curveball." How\'d THAT happen? Simple! When you enter the Pokémon capture screen, instead of just flicking your ball forward you\'ll want to tap it and hold, then spin it around in a circle (several times) before flicking it toward the Pokémon. You\'ll know you\'re doing it right when the Pokéball gets a bit of a glimmer to it, like sparks are coming off the ball.</string>
    <string name="desc_3">You may also notice that, while catching Pokémon, you\'re occasionally getting a "Great throw" bonus. That\'s because you totally nailed the throw and hit the Pokémon with your Pokéball within the ever-shrinking yellow circle hover over the front of the Pokémon.That\'s right: the yellow ring is more than just an idea of where to throw your Pokéball. It\'s specifically a target to nail to get a throw bonus! (Note: With difficult to capture Pokémon, the ring will be orange or red — that\'s a visual indicator that you may want to use a Razzberry to make the Pokémon easier to capture.)</string>
    <string name="desc_4">If you\'re in the middle of a contentious Pokémon capture, and you\'ve thrown Pokéball after Pokéball to no avail, you may want to throw said Pokémon a delicious raspberry (er, "Razz Berry"). You can buy Razz Berries with in-game money, but you also earn them from visiting Pokéstops pretty frequently. I currently have 21, have used a bunch, and never bought any. BEWARE: The Razz Berry will only make the Pokémon easier to capture for your next throw. Make it count!</string>
    <string name="desc_5">You\'ve gotten some eggs at this point, no doubt. You may even have found them hidden in the Pokémon submenu (after clicking the Pokéball). Now that you\'ve got those eggs incubating, it\'s time to start walking! Ah, but you\'ve got a car — not so fast Pokéfriend! It\'s true that you\'ll need to cover a distance to get that egg incubated (anywhere from 2KM to 10KM), but you\'ll also need to do it under a relatively low speed. The game can tell that you\'re in a car, because people don\'t run much faster than 25MPH (and that\'s people like Usain Bolt, not you and me). Also, hey, don\'t play "Pokémon GO" while driving. Stop that. This also rules out trains/buses/etc. But there is one method that\'s slightly easier than walking and a lot less dangerous than slowly driving around: biking. Get on your bicycle and get incubating! (NOTE: You\'ll need to keep the app open and your phone screen on to have the distance you cover count for anything. Sorry!)</string>
    <string name="desc_6">As it turns out, walking around with your phone\'s screen on full blast is a great way to decimate your battery. "Pokémon GO" has a solution buried in its settings menu. Tap the Pokéball, select "Settings" in the upper right corner, then click "Battery Saver." Solved!</string>
    <string name="desc_7">If you want to walk around with your phone in your pocket and still capture that sweet, sweet distance you\'ll need to incubate eggs (and hatch new Pokémon), simply set your phone\'s screen to never turn off and slide it into your pocket upside down. If you\'ve already got the game set to "Battery Saver" mode, the phone will register it\'s been flipped over and automatically dim the screen (like you see above). Magical!</string>
    <string name="desc_8">Having a hard time finding Pokémon? Take advantage of other people\'s good fortunes by going to a Pokéstop that has a "module" attached. These modules attract Pokémon to the stop for 30 minutes at a time. Better yet, they affect anyone walking by that Pokéstop. Nothing like scooping up some free Pokémon from someone else\'s item!</string>
    <string name="desc_9">If you open the Pokémon menu in the lower right, you\'ll notice that there are a handful of footprints beneath each Pokémon. You may also notice that one of the Pokémon silhouettes doesn\'t have any footprints, which means it\'s really close to you. If you tap that silhouette, the Pokémon will be revealed on your map! Voila!</string>
    <string name="desc_10">Instead of powering up your un-evolved Pokémon, focus on evolving them into their final form first. They\'ll automatically become more powerful just from evolving, and you use the same stuff (candy, star dust) to power up that you do to evolve. Given that, you should focus your energy on evolving Pokémon first — the more resource-intensive of the two steps anyway — before powering up.</string>
    <string name="desc_11">Tired of catching the same Weedle over and over? I sympathize, but don\'t let your boredom get in the way of evolving and powering up your other Pokémon. The more Pokémon you collect, the more candy you\'ll earn for that type of Pokémon. And the more candy you have, the faster you can evolve and power up your Pokémon. And the more evolved/higher the power your Pokémon are, the better you\'ll do in gym battles! Bonus: You\'ll get stardust every time you capture new Pokémon. And what\'s stardust used for? Evolving and powering up Pokémon.</string>
    <string name="desc_12">When you tap the Pokéball and enter the Pokémon submenu, things can get disorganized quickly. Good news: There\'s a super easy way to organize it by a few different metrics. Perhaps you\'d like to organize it alphabetically, or by combat points? You totally can. Click the icon in the lower right hand corner of the main Pokémon menu and you\'ll find a few different ways of organizing your Pokémon. Convenient! Also, really helpful when you want to, say, decide which Pokémon you should power up (the one with the most CP already, obvz). </string>
    <string name="desc_13">If you get a Lucky egg, it allows you to earn double experience points for 30 minutes. Two easy ways to earn a lot of XP points are by catching or evolving Pokémon. Catching a new Pokémon gives you 100 XP. Evolving Pokémon gives you 500 XP. When you have the Lucky Egg in play, you\'ll gain 200 XP for any new captures and 1,000 XP for any evolution. If you have a lot of Pokémon to evolve wait to do it until you have a Lucky Egg. Why add the incense or lure modules? Those attract Pokémon for 30 minutes exactly. Time a Lucky Egg to go at the same time as a Pokémon lure and start watching the experience points roll in as Pokémon after Pokémon comes to you.</string>
    <string name="desc_14">Pokemon Game Download :- <a href="http://www.apkmirror.com/apk/niantic-inc/pokemon-go/pokemon-go-0-29-2-release/pokemon-go-0-29-2-android-apk-download/">Click To Download.</a>http://www.apkmirror.com/apk/niantic-inc/pokemon-go/pokemon-go-0-29-2-release/pokemon-go-0-29-2-android-apk-download/</string>


    <!-- AdMob ad unit IDs -->
    <string name="banner_bottom_first">ca-app-pub-7549032521180309/4895776670</string>
    <string name="banner_bottom_second">ca-app-pub-7549032521180309/6372509870</string>
    <string name="interstitial_first">ca-app-pub-7549032521180309/7849243075</string>
    <string name="interstitial_second"> ca-app-pub-7549032521180309/9325976276</string>
    <string name="nativ_first">ca-app-pub-7549032521180309/1802709475</string>


</resources>
